- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_00_B
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_01
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Legwear_20
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_01_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Grace_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_01B
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_01
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_01B_LearnSoulwardens_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_02_Rumors
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 17.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_02
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_01B
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_02_Rumors_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 19.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_03
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_02
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_03_ClimbArcturus_complete_available_response_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Adiana_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_04
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_03
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: amethystcutt2
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_04_ToAdiana_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Adiana_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_05
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_04
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Chestwear_20
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_05_UnblockFountain_complete_available_response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 20.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Adiana_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_06
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_05
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_06_CorruptionTincture_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 21.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Adiana_00
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_07
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_06
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: Azoth_Vessel
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_07_CorruptedPlans_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 21.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_08
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_07
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Footwear_20
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_08_ToYonas_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 21.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_09
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_08
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Handwear_20
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_09_GetHaft_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 23.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99A_MSQ_10
  RequiredAchievementId: 99A_MSQ_09
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_proposal_prompt_next"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_10_GetCrosspiece_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 24.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_01
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_19
  RequiredAchievementId: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT2
  ItemRewardQty: 5.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_11_ForgeStaff_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 24.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Captain
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_19a
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_19
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_incomplete_a"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_12_ReturnStaff_complete_available_response_a_new"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 25.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_20
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_19a
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: CRX_RewardContainerT3_Chestwear_30
  ItemRewardQty: 1.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_start_prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_proposal_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_proposal_c_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_13_UseStaff_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 25.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_21
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_20
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: PotionHealthT3
  ItemRewardQty: 10.0
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_start_prompt_new"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_proposal_new"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_incomplete_new"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_14_HeartgemGroup_complete_available_response"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: ""
- ObjectiveID: 99A_MSQ_15_Ritual
  Type: MainStoryQuest
  Difficulty: ""
  DifficultyLevel: 25.0
  MaxInfluenceLevel: ""
  FlagPvp: ""
  CanBeShared: ""
  CanFastTravel: ""
  Task: 99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_container
  NpcDestinationId: 99A_Yonas_02
  ExclusiveTerritory: ""
  AchievementId: 99_MSQ_22
  RequiredAchievementId: 99_MSQ_21
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  SuccessGameEventId: 99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_success
  FailureGameEventId: ""
  ProgressionReward: ""
  ExperienceReward: ""
  ObjectiveReward: ""
  ItemRewardName: ""
  ItemRewardQty: null
  ShouldResetOnFactionChange: ""
  Repeatable: ""
  CanBeAbandoned: false
  Title: "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_title"
  Description: "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_objective_desc"
  PlayerPrompt: "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_start_prompt"
  ObjectiveProposalResponse: "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_proposal_a"
  InProgressResponse: "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_incomplete"
  DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt: "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT"
  DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse: "@99A_MSQ_15_Ritual_complete_available_response_a"
  ObjectiveCompletionResponse: ""
  ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse: ""
  HideIncompleteTurninMarker: true
  ORMReleaseEventTags: ""
  ORMReleaseActiveOverride: ""
  SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid: ""
  EntitlementId: ""
  QuestArcTag: ""
  HideAvailableMapIcon : ""
  NOTE: Soul Trial
